alfabb.com 2008-06-19

# AlfaBB Privacy & Terms of Use

## AlfaBB.com Privacy Statement & Terms of Use

**Terms of Use**

Please read this notice before using our site. By using the site, you agree to abide by these Terms of Use; please do not use our site if you do not agree with the Terms of Use outlined below. AlfaBB reserves the right to modify the Terms of Use at its sole discretion, and by using this site, you agree to be bound by the modifications or updates to the Terms of Use. 

**Privacy Notice**

AlfaBB values your privacy. To keep you informed, we have created this privacy statement that discloses our purposes and methods for online collection and use of information. This statement applies to all information collected through the AlfaBB.com website and information gathered from any web pages that we host. 

**Types of Information Collected**

Generally, personal information is not collected from visitors to the AlfaBB website. However, in order to access certain special services, personal information is requested; those cases are described in more detail below. 

**Bulletin Board Registration**

AlfaBB requires a valid e-mail address for users who want to participate in the AlfaBB Discussion Forums. This allows us to protect our community from abusive postings and provides a verifiable point of contact should legal questions arise. At any time, you have the ability to keep your e-mail address hidden from other users by selecting that option within your user profile. 

Also in the forum registration, you have the option of providing some additional information such as occupation, interests, and homepage URL. This information is made available to other bulletin board users to foster a sense of community. If you have any concerns about providing this information, simply leave the fields blank and your registration will still be processed. 

**Cookies**

Certain activities on the AlfaBB website involve the use of "cookies" to facilitate your experience. This includes retention of your username and password for the AlfaBB forums and showing a default Topic View when you visit the forums. You have the option to turn these cookies off at any time by updating your user profile preferences. If your browser doesn’t support cookies, or if you have cookies turned off, these preferences will not be set. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

AlfaBB does not disclose your personally identifying information to any third parties for any purpose without your prior consent. All reasonable care is taken to ensure its security both offline and online. 

It’s also important to be aware that when you voluntarily provide personal information (e.g., address, phone number) in a posting on the bulletin board, that information is publicly available and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we encourage using caution before offering of any personally identifying information within the message board itself. 

**Changing or Updating Personal Information**

You can update or change your user profile on the AlfaBB by clicking on the "usercp>edit profile" link on the sites home page. 

If you have questions regarding your information, you can contact our Privacy Administrator via [this page](http://www.alfabb.com/bb/forums/sendmessage.php).
